Guide to the Irish Repertory Theatre Records AIA.080
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Irish Repertory Theatre Records
1988-ongoing
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Irish Repertory Theatre
O'Reilly, Ciarán
AIA.080
27.5 Linear Feet in 32 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 10 record cartons, 1 flat box, 3 oversize flat boxes, and 2 flat file folders
25 VHS
20 Digital_Betacam
317 Gigabytes in 73,500 computer files
4 websites in 4 archived websites.
The Irish Repertory Theatre (IRT) was founded in New York, New York in 1988 by Charlotte Moore and Ciarán O'Reilly. The IRT produces Irish and Irish-American plays and musicals year-round. The Irish Repertory Theatre Records document 28 seasons of productions, from 1988 to 2016. Productions include The Plough and the Stars, The Irish...And How They Got That Way, and Finian's Rainbow. The records contain press and marketing materials, correspondence, scripts, legal documents, financial documents, original artwork, video recordings, and posters. The material consists of paper, born-digital, websites, and audiovisual material.
Scope and Contents
The Irish Repertory Theatre (IRT) Records document 28 seasons of productions staged by the Theatre, from 1988 to 2016. Productions include The Plough and the Stars, The Irish...And How They Got That Way, and Finian's Rainbow. The records document the work of various members and departments of the IRT, including Ciaran O'Reilly, the Producing Director; the Marketing Department; the General Manager; the Literary Department; and the Membership Manager. The records contain press and marketing materials, correspondence, scripts, legal documents, financial documents, original artwork, videos, and posters. The material consists of paper, born-digital, the website, and audiovisual recordings. The press and marketing materials constitute the bulk of the collection and include programs, press releases, photographs, slides, and video recordings of productions and the IRT's annual benefits. The correspondence includes rejection letters; negotiations for rights, licensing, and productions; and communications with actors, producers, directors, and IRT members. The collection includes scripts used in productions and those submitted for the New Works Reading Series. The legal documents include contracts as well as court documents from legal proceedings in which the IRT was involved. The financial records include season and production budgets, and box office receipts and statements. The original artwork includes paintings and drawings for set designs and posters.
Arrangement
The records are arranged into the following five series, with two of these series further arranged into subseries.
Series I. Production Materials, 1989-2016
Series II. New Works Reading Series, 2005-2014
Subseries II. A. Selected Plays, 2006-2014 Subseries II. B. Rejected Script Files, 2005-2014
Series III. Administrative Records, 1990-2013
Subseries III. A. General Administrative Records, 1990-2013 Subseries III. B. Producing Director Records, 1994-2003 Subseries III. C. General Manager Records, 1997-2004 Subseries III. D. Membership Manager Records, 1999-2004 Subseries III.E. Marketing Department Records, 2003-2016
Series IV. Financial and Legal Records, 1989-2010
Series V. Archived Websites, September 2019-ongoing
Historical Note
The Irish Repertory Theatre (IRT) was founded in New York, New York in 1988 by Charlotte Moore and Ciarán O'Reilly. As of 2018, Moore is the Artistic Director and O'Reilly is the Managing Director. The two met in the late 1980s in a Hudson Guild Theater production of Hugh Leonard's Summer, and decided to collaborate on a production of Sean O'Casey's The Plough and the Stars in September 1988. Their profits from that production were enough to stage another show, and in this way the IRT was founded. The IRT produces Irish and Irish-American plays and musicals year-round, both classics of Irish theater as well as new works by emerging Irish and Irish-American writers. The Theatre moved to its current location, as of 2018, in the Chelsea neighborhood of Manhattan in 1995. The IRT, its staff, and their productions have garnered critical acclaim and industry awards for their work.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions, with the exception of certain files pertaining to legal proceedings in Series IV.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact [repository contact information] with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Ciarán O'Reilly in June 2016. The accession number associated with this gift is 2016.055.
In 2019, http://irishrep.org/ was added to the web archive through the use of Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. The accession number associated with this website is 2019.143. In October 2021, https://www.youtube.com/c/IrishRep/videos/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2022.017. In September 2023, https://www.youtube.com/@IrishRep/videos/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2023.087. In October 2024, https://irishrepertorytheatre.passgallery.com/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2024.065.
In March 2025, Marion Casey transferred an accretion consisting of a mounted, oversized poster for the production of The Shaughraun; the accession number associated with this transfer is 2025.029.
Custodial History
The collection was transferred to Bobst Library from the Irish Repertory Theatre offices at 132 West 22nd Street, New York, NY 10011 on June 30, 2016. It was arranged by season, boxed and inventoried by Jessica Layman (Director of Marketing), in consultation with Lisa Fane (General Manager). Much of the collection was in temporary storage with The Padded Wagon, in the company's temporary offices at 345 Park Avenue, 17th floor, NYC, or in the company's temporary performance space at Theatre DR2, 103 East 15th Street while their permanent home was under renovation from 2014-2016.
Appraisal
Items of little research value were deaccessioned, including personal financial documents related to performers and customers, files related to staff performance, unopened commercial recordings of music and audiobooks unrelated to the Irish Repertory Theatre, clippings of reviews, Zip and floppy disks containing graphic design files used to create promotional ephemera for productions, and Theatre souvenirs. Off-air recordings of reviews of IRT productions were deaccessioned.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Separated Materials
One recording of The Irish...And How They Got That Way on VHS was transferred to the Avery Fisher Center in July 2018.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Theater programs.; Photographs.; Slides (photographs); Theater -- Production and direction.; Repertory theater -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th century.; Irish drama.; Off-Broadway theater; Repertory theater -- New York (State) -- New York -- 21st century.; Theater management -- New York (State) -- New York; Web sites.; O'Reilly, Ciarán
- Series I. Production Materials, 1988-2010; 9.5 Linear Feet in 14 manuscript boxes, 2 record cartons, 3 oversize flat boxes; 98 Gigabytes in 24,739 computer files; 25 VHS; 20 Digital_Betacam; 12 CDs
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in chronological order by season, with no arrangement within each season.
  Scope and Contents
  This series documents 28 seasons of the Irish Repertory Theatre's productions and annual benefits, from 1989 to 2016. Material in this series consists of paper, born-digital, and audiovisual formats and includes promotional material, photographs, artwork, and material pertaining to legal and creative issues from early productions. The promotional material includes programs, postcards, posters, and press releases for individual productions; tickets, invitations, and programs for annual benefits; and issues of Prologue, the IRT's newsletter. The audiovisual material consists of video and digital audio and video recordings of select productions, including George M. Cohan Tonight!, Noctu, The Irish...And How They Got That Way, and annual benefits. Most productions are well documented through digital and print photographs and slides. Artwork includes drawings for set designs and posters.
  - 1988-1989 Season -- I Do Not Like Thee, Dr. Fell, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - 1988-1989 Season -- The Plough and the Stars (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
  - 1988-1989 Season -- Yeats: A Celebration in His Own Words with Music and Song (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - 1988-1989 Season -- A Whistle in the Dark, 080.0011
    - Paper (Box 1, Folder 8, Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0011)
  - 1989-1990 Season -- Sea Marks (Box 1, Folder 9, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1989-1990 Season -- English That For Me! (Box 1, Folder 10-11, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1989-1990 Season -- Endwords (Box 1, Folder 12, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1989-1990 Season -- Philadelphia, Here I Come! (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
  - 1989-1990 Season -- A Tribute to Samuel Beckett (Box 1, Folder 17-18, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 1)
  - 1990-1991 Season -- Playboy of the Western World
    - Paper (Box 1, Folder 19-20, Box 2, Folder 1, Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0018)
  - 1990-1991 Season -- Making History, 080.0015
    - Paper (Box 2, Folder 2-5, Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0015)
  - 1990-1991 Season -- Benefit at Town Hall (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1990-1991 Season -- Yeats: A Celebration! (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1990-1991 Season -- Alive, Alive Oh!, 080.0010
    - Paper (Box 2, Folder 8, Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0010)
  - 1991-1992 Season -- Grandchild of Kings, 1991-1993; 080.0009
    - Paper (Box 2, Folder 9-18, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 1)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0009)
  - 1992-1993 Season -- The Madame Macadam Traveling Theatre (Box 2, Folder 19-20, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1992-1993 Season -- Joyicity and Frankly Brendan (Box 3, Folder 1-2, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1992-1993 Season -- Seconds Out (Box 3, Folder 3-9, Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1993-1994 Season -- Yeats: A Celebration! (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - 1993-1994 Season -- The Au Pair Man, 080.0008
    - Paper (Box 3, Folder 12-13, Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0008)
  - 1994-1995 Season -- Mother of All the Behans (Box 3, Folder 14, Folder 16, Box 32, Folder 15)
  - 1994-1995 Season -- Alive, Alive Oh!
    - Paper (Box 3, Folder 15-16, Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0004)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- Same Old Moon
    - Paper (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0005)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- Juno and the Paycock (Box 3, Folder 21, Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- Frank Pig Says Hello (Box 4, Folder 2-5, Box 32, Folder 15)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- Shimmer (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- A Whistle in the Dark (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- Da
    - Paper (Box 4, Folder 10-11, Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0037)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- A Wilde Night on Broadway! (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1995-1996 Season -- 1996 Benefit -- Yeats: A Celebration! (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- Bein' With Behan (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- The Importance of Being Earnest (Box 4, Folder 15-17, Box 32, Folder 14)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- Yeats on Stage: The Plays (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- My Astonishing Self
    - Paper (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_1
  - 1996-1997 Season -- Mass Appeal
    - Paper (Box 4, Folder 22-24, Box 5, Folder 1, Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0038)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- Wait 'til I Tell You: An Evening with Carmel Quinn
    - Paper (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_2
  - 1996-1997 Season -- The Plough and the Stars (Box 5, Folder 3-5)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- The Nightingale and Not the Lark and The Invisible Man (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
  - 1996-1997 Season -- 1997 Benefit (Box 33, Cassette 080.0016)
  - 1997-1998 Season -- Song At Sunset, 1996-1998; 080.0041
    - Paper Materials (Box 5, Folder 9-11)
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0041)
  - 1997-1998 Season -- Major Barbara (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - 1997-1998 Season -- Rafferty Rescues the Moon
    - Paper (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0006-080.0007)
  - 1997-1998 Season -- Long Day's Journey into Night (Box 5, Folder 15-18)
  - 1997-1998 Season -- The Irish…And How They Got That Way, 1997-2000
    - Paper (Box 5, Folder 19-28, Box 6, Folder 1-10, Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0012-080.0013, Box 34, Cassette 080.0034-080.0036, Box 35, Cassette 080.0043-080.0045, Box 36, Cassette 080.0046)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_211
  - 1997-1998 Season -- 1998 Benefit
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0040)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_61
  - 1998-1999 Season -- The Happy Prince (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- The Shaughraun (Box 6, Folder 12, Box 32, Folder 14, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- Krapp's Last Tape
    - Paper (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0022)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- Oh, Coward!
    - Paper (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0014)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- The Shadow of a Gunman (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- Dear Liar (Box 6, Folder 16, Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1998-1999 Season -- 1999 Benefit -- How the Irish Saved Civilization, 1997-1999
    - Paper (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0001, Box 34, Cassette 080.0028-080.0033)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_62
  - 1999-2000 Season -- Invasions and Legacies
    - Paper (Box 7, Folder 3-6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_4
  - 1999-2000 Season -- Eclipsed (Box 7, Folder 7-10, Box 32, Folder 14)
  - 1999-2000 Season -- The Irish…And How They Got That Way (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
  - 1999-2000 Season -- Our Lady of Sligo
    - Paper (Box 7, Folder 14-18)
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0042)
  - 1999-2000 Season -- The Country Boy (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - 1999-2000 Season -- Don Juan in Hell
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_3
  - 1999-2000 Season -- 2000 Benefit -- Song of the Century
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Video (Box 34, Cassette 080.0023-080.0027)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_63
  - 2000-2001 Season -- The Importance of Being Oscar (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2000-2001 Season -- The Picture of Dorian Gray (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - 2000-2001 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2000-2001 Season -- The Hostage (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
  - 2000-2001 Season -- A Life
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_5
  - 2000-2001 Season -- The Irish…And How They Got That Way, 2001-2002
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 13-14, Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_6
  - 2001-2002 Season -- That and the Cup of Tea: An Evening with Carmel Quinn (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- Circasia! A Celtic Circus
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0019)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- An Evening in New York with W.B. Yeats and John Quinn, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- Save It For the Stage: The Life of Reilly (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- The Streets of New York
    - Paper (Box 8, Folder 19-22, Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_7
  - 2001-2002 Season -- The Matchmaker (Box 8, Folder 23-24, Box 32, Folder 13, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- The Playboy of the Western World (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- Pigtown (Box 9, Folder 3-5)
  - 2001-2002 Season -- 2002 Benefit -- Sunset and Evening Star
    - Paper (Box 9, Folder 6, Box 33)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0020)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- Bailegangáire (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- A Celtic Christmas
    - Paper (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_8
  - 2002-2003 Season -- The Love-Hungry Farmer (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 32, Folder 13)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- Peg O' My Heart (Box 9, Folder 11-12, Box 32, Folder 17)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- Bedbound (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- Foley (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
  - 2002-2003 Season -- 2003 Benefit -- Finian's Rainbow
    - Paper (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_64
  - 2003-2004 Season -- The Colleen Bawn
    - Paper (Box 9, Folder 18, Box 32, Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_12
  - 2003-2004 Season -- Christmas with Tommy Makem (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 2003-2004 Season -- Eden
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Video (Box 33, Cassette 080.0021)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_9
  - 2003-2004 Season -- Let's Put on a Show!
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_11
  - 2003-2004 Season -- Finian's Rainbow, 2001-2005
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 4-10)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_10
  - 2003-2004 Season -- 2004 Benefit -- Bloom (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 2003-2004 Season -- Playing Burton (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2004-2005 Season -- Triptych
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_17
  - 2004-2005 Season -- Philadelphia, Here I Come!
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_15
  - 2004-2005 Season -- Endgame
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_14
  - 2004-2005 Season -- After the Ball
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_13
  - 2004-2005 Season -- She Stoops to Conquer
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_16
  - 2004-2005 Season -- 2005 Benefit -- A Cabaret of Stars (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - 2005-2006 Season -- A Concert for Concern (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 2005-2006 Season -- Mr. Dooley's America
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_20
  - 2005-2006 Season -- The Field
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_23
  - 2005-2006 Season -- George M. Cohan Tonight!, 2005-2008
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_19
  - 2005-2006 Season -- Mrs. Warren's Profession
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_21
  - 2005-2006 Season -- Beowulf
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_18
  - 2005-2006 Season -- The Bells of Christmas, TW_AIA_080_ER_22
  - 2005-2006 Season -- You Don't Have To Be Irish (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2005-2006 Season -- 2006 Benefit -- A Cabaret of Stars II (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2006-2007 Season -- The Hairy Ape
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_29
  - 2006-2007 Season -- Meet Me In St. Louis
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_27
  - 2006-2007 Season -- Great White American Teeth and Swansong
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_26
  - 2006-2007 Season -- Tom Crean: Antarctic Explorer (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 2006-2007 Season -- Defender of the Faith
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_24
  - 2006-2007 Season -- Gaslight
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 15, Box Shared Tamiment 002, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_25
  - 2006-2007 Season -- 2007 Benefit (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 2007-2008 Season -- Sive
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_33
  - 2007-2008 Season -- The Devil's Disciple
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_35
  - 2007-2008 Season -- Take Me Along
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_34
  - 2007-2008 Season -- Prisoner of the Crown
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_32
  - 2007-2008 Season -- Around the World in 80 Days
    - Paper (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_31
  - 2007-2008 Season -- 20th Anniversary Gala (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 2008-2009 Season -- The Master Builder
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_39
  - 2008-2009 Season -- Confessions of an Irish Publican
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_38
  - 2008-2009 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_30
  - 2008-2009 Season -- Aristocrats
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 4, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 2, Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_37
  - 2008-2009 Season -- The Yeats Project
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_41
  - 2008-2009 Season -- The Rivalry
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_40
  - 2008-2009 Season -- After Luke and When I Was God
    - Paper (Box 12, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 008, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_AIA_080_ER_36
  - 2008-2009 Season -- New Works Reading Series (Box 12, Folder 8)